Amazing...!
‫مذهل‬
Vito, what are you doing?
‫ما الذي تفعله يا فيتو؟‬
Father, it's amazing!
‫هذا مذهل أيها الأب‬
The president of the WEN and Germa's boss are talking-rero !
‫رئيس صحيفة الاقتصاد العالمية وزعيم جيرما يتحدثان-ريرو‬
Of course, they talk. They both have ears and mouths.
‫هذا طبيعي، كلاهما يمتلكان أذن وحنجرة‬
Still, what a party-rero !
‫ولكنها حفلة استثنائية‬
Eldest son and minister of candy: Perospero.
‫الابن الأكبر؛ وزير الحلوى بيروسبيرو‬
Eldest daughter and the minister of fruit: Compote.
‫الابنة الكبرى؛ وزيرة الفواكه كومبوت‬
Second son: Sweet Commander Katakuri.
‫الابن الثاني؛ قائد الحلوى كاتاكوري‬
Fourteenth daughter: Sweet Commander Smoothie.
‫الابنة 14؛ قائدة الحلوى سموذي‬
Third son: Daifuku. Fourth son: Oven.
‫الابن الثالث دايفوكو، والابن الرابع أوفن‬
Countless monsters are gathered here...
‫الكثير من الوحوش في الجوار‬
It was reassuring to have them as allies,
‫كونهم بصفنا كان أمرًا يبعث الطمأنينة في قلبي‬
so it's crazy to think that they'll be our enemies soon-rero.
‫ولكن فكرة أنهم سيكونون أعدائنا ترعبني حقًّا-ريرو‬
Huh? "Enemies"?
‫أعداء؟‬
If you have time to worry, go check downstairs!
‫إذا كان لديك الوقت للتفكير‬ ‫اذهب لتفقّد الطابق السفلي‬
Okay, Father. Let's go, Gotti.
‫حاضر أيها الأب، لنذهب يا غوتي‬
I heard that the wedding cake will be very fancy.
‫سمعت أنّ كعكة الزواج ستكون فاخرة للغاية‬
Mama.
‫ماما‬
Here is Mother Carmel.
‫ها هي الأم كارمل‬
Yes... My beloved...
‫أجل، حبيبتنا...‬
Mother!
‫الأم‬
Oh, it's always nice to see her smiling brightly.
‫كم يسعدني رؤية الأم تبتسم بإشراق كالمعتاد‬
She's like the sun.
‫إنها كالشمس الدافئة‬
That's right. Mother is the light of this world!
‫هذا صحيح، الأم هي بريق هذا العالم‬
No one knows who she is, though...
‫رغم أنني لا أعلم من تكون‬
This is my first tea party, so I am not familiar...
‫هذه أول حفلة شاي لي، ولكن بخصوص هذه السيدة‬
You should really...
‫لا تحشر نفسك...‬
mind your own business!
‫في ذكرياتي العزيزة‬
Cheers!
‫بصحتكم‬
How's everything going down there?
‫كيف تجري الأمور لديكم في الأسفل؟‬
The cooks finished preparing for the tea party, so they're enjoying a banquet.
‫الطهاة انتهوا من التجهيزات الخاصة بحفلة الشاي‬ ‫لذا هم يحتفلون ويشربون‬
We blocked all passages in the meantime.
‫لقد أغلقنا الممرات أثناء احتفالهم‬
Good. With that done, nobody will be able to come up here for a while.
‫جيد، لا يمكن لأحد أن يصعد للأعلى‬ ‫لفترة وجيزة بما أنكم أغلقتم الممرات‬
Now we'll set the horned transponder snails to jam radio signals and isolate the venue.
‫سنُنصّب حلازين الاتصال المقرنة‬ ‫لتشويش إشارات الاتصال وعزل الموقع‬
Don't forget to set up for "you-know-what," too.
‫لا تنسى تنصيب ما أخبرتك به أيضًا‬
Yes, sir.
‫حاضر‬
In honor of your daughter's wedding, we brought you a present, Charlotte.
‫أحضرت لكِ هدية بمناسبة زواج ابنتك يا شارلوت‬
Oh, a treasure chest!
‫إنه صندوق كنز‬
My favorite!
‫نوعي المفضل‬
I wonder what's inside.
‫ماذا بداخله يا تُرى؟‬
I, too, brought you a present, Linlin.
‫أتيت بهدية أيضًا يا لينلين‬
Take one from me too!
‫لتقبلي هديتي أيضًا‬
Mine's something rare from the south.
‫هديتي نادرة جلبتها من الجنوب‬
Well, mine is from the farthest reaches of the north.
‫لقد ذهبت إلى أقاصي الشمال من أجل هديتي‬
I'm so grateful! It's always a pleasure to get so many presents!
‫أنا ممتنة لحصولي على هذا الكم من الهدايا دائمًا‬
Thank you!
‫شكرًا لكم‬
I'm so happy!
‫أنا في غاية السعادة‬
Speaking of treasure chests, Mamigo, I heard you've obtained a great undersea treasure.
‫بالحديث عن صناديق الكنز يا ماميغو‬ ‫سمعت أنكِ حصلتِ على كنز عظيم من أعماق البحر‬ ‫مورغانز يخاطبها بماما + ميغو، وميغو تعني صديق‬
Word reached you quickly. That's my Morgans!
‫الأخبار تصلك بسرعة، كما هو متوقع منك يا مورغانز‬
It's true.
‫أصبت‬
I now possess a chest that has been an heirloom for generations of undersea royalty!
‫صندوق الكنز الذي تم توارثه‬ ‫لأجيال بين السلالة الملكية لأعماق البحر‬
Neptune actually let it slip from his grasp.
‫لسببٍ أجهله، تخلّى عنه نبتون وهو الآن بحوزتي هنا‬
The legendary...
‫إنه الصندوق الأسطوري...‬
Tamate Box!
‫صندوق تاماتي‬
Oh! Look how fancy it is!
‫يا لفخامته‬
What's in it?
‫ماذا بداخله؟‬
Have you opened it yet, Mamigo?!
‫هل قمتِ بفتحه يا ماميغو؟‬
I'm saving it for the feast after Pudding's wedding,
‫أثناء الوليمة الكبرى بعد زفاف بودينغ‬
I'll open all the presents for everyone to see!
‫سأقوم بفتحه بحضوركم جميعًا وأريكم ما بداخله‬
Father!
‫الأب‬
Oh, you all done?
‫هل انتهيتم؟‬
Everything is ready-rero.
‫التجهيزات مكتملة‬
Okay. Good job.
‫أحسنتم عملًا‬
Guys, go get changed.
‫اذهبوا لتبديل ملابسكم يا رجال‬
Yes, sir.
‫حاضر‬
Caesar, bring out the mirror.
‫سيزار، اخرج معك المرآة‬
You jerk! Don't call me that!
‫لقد قلتَ ذلك الاسم مجددًا أيها الوغد‬
So this is the entrance to the tea party.
‫هذا هو مدخل حفلة الشاي إذًا‬
Enjoy it while you can, scumbags!
‫استمتعوا بهذه الحفلة قدر الإمكان أيها الحثالة‬
Caesar Clown?
‫سيزار كلاون؟‬
You're scum too.
‫أنت حثالة أيضًا‬
Just hide that mirror somewhere already.
‫أخفي تلك المرآة في مكان ما وحسب‬
Shut up! I know what I'm doing!
‫اخرس، أعلم ذلك‬
When Big Mom starts shrieking,
‫مهمتك تقتضي في جلب تلك المرآة‬ ‫للقاعة عندما تبدأ بيغ مام بالصراخ‬
That's our only escape route.
‫إنها مخرجنا الوحيد‬
So be sure to not get any ideas.
‫لذا إياك وأن تتصرف بطيش‬
It's too late for me to betray you!
‫من المبكر أن أخونك‬
This is bad! Bege and his crew are up to something!
‫مصيبة، بيجي ومن معه يخططون لمكيدة‬
I carved it off.
‫أجهزت عليها‬
Information leaks will bring unexpected crises.
‫أي تسريب للمعلومات سيؤدي إلى أزمات غير متوقعة‬
The ceremony starts in 30 minutes.
‫تبقت 30 دقيقة لحفل الزواج‬
Are Straw Hat and his crew ready? He better not be fooling around again...
‫هل طاقم قبعة القش وجينبي مستعدون؟‬
Check for yourself! They're in your body!
‫تفقد أمورهم بنفسك، هم بداخل جسدك‬
Hey, you fools! Why're you sleeping?!
‫يا أوغاد، لِمَ أنتم نائمون؟‬
You should be getting ready!
‫يجدر بكم الاستعداد‬
Let them sleep.
‫دعهم ينامون‬
They haven't had time to rest since they arrived.
‫يبدو أنهم لم يناموا منذ وصولهم‬
I'll wake them up 10 minutes before.
‫سأوقظهم قبل الموعد بعشر دقائق‬
I can't believe this.
‫لا أصدق هذا‬
If they become a burden, I'll abandon them immediately.
‫سأتخلص منهم إن أفسدوا خطتي‬
Don't worry.
‫لا تقلق‬
I'll get everything ready for them.
‫إنني أتكفل بكل من المراقبة والاستعداد‬
Those idiots... How ridiculous.
‫أولئك الأوغاد لا يُعتمد عليهم‬
Right!
‫أرأيت؟‬
You need to go back inside.
‫يجب أن تعود للداخل‬
I'm gonna go into the hall.
‫سأذهب للقاعة‬
Everyone, prepare yourselves!
‫استعدوا جميعًا‬
Once we enter,
‫حينما نبدأ...‬
there's no turning back!
‫لا مجال للتراجع‬
I hope you're ready too...
‫آمل أن تكون مستعدًا أنت الآخر...‬
Vinsmoke Sanji!
‫يا فينسموك سانجي‬
I...
‫أنا...‬
I wasn't planning on getting married when I came here so...
‫لم أكن أنوي الزواج حينما وصلت إلى هنا...‬
it's really surreal for me to see you like this...
‫ولكن مجاورتك بهذا الشكل يُعد غريبًا عليّ‬
I feel like I'm dreaming...
‫أشعر وكأنني في حلم‬
Stay cool, stay cool.
‫ابقَ هادئًا، ابقَ هادئًا‬
I won't be fooled again.
‫لن أُخدع مجددًا‬
Is it...
‫أهو...‬
a good dream or a bad dream?
‫حلم جيد أم سيئ؟‬
Oh man, she's so cute!
‫إنها ظريفة فعلًا‬
Of... O-O-Of course, it's a good dream!
‫بـ -بـ-بالطبع حلم جيد‬
Really?! That's a relief!
‫حقًّا؟ هذا جيد‬
Hey, calm down!
‫اهدأي يا نفسي‬
She's just acting!
‫إنها تمثّل هذا الدور وحسب‬
She's planning to kill you!
‫إنها تنوي قتلي‬
Unless, I really was just dreaming...
‫ربما كنتُ أحلم حقًّا...‬
No, no, no! Don't be fooled! You know the truth!
‫كلا، لا تنخدع، صدّق ما رأيته آنذاك‬
Sanji-san, is there something wrong?
‫سانجي-سان، أثمة خطب ما؟‬
What? N-No, no, no, no! It's just...
‫ماذا؟، كلا، كلا، كل ما في الأمر...‬
That's right!
‫صحيح‬
A-About the wedding kiss... Um...
‫بـ-بخصوص قبلة الزواج...‬
I was thinking that If you're embarrassed... doing it in front of all those people...
‫إذا كانت لديكِ مشكلة في فعلها للمرة الأولى أمام الحضور...‬
I-I-I could maybe kiss you on the forehead instead...
‫فـ-فلا مانع لدي في تقبيلك على جبينك أو...‬
It's okay to kiss me on the lips. We're gonna be husband and wife.
‫قبلني على شفتي، فنحن سنصبح زوجان‬
What was that noise?!
‫ما كان هذا؟‬
Prince Sanji crashed into the ceiling?!
‫سانجي-ساما اصطدم في السقف؟‬
How did that happen?
‫كيف انتهى به الحال هكذا؟‬
He's bleeding so much!
‫إنه ينزف بشدة‬
Oh, no!
‫مصيبة‬
Sanji-san !
‫سانجي-سان‬
What's wrong with this perverted imp?!
‫ما بال هذا المنحرف اللعين؟‬
I can't wait to blow him away!
‫أريد قتله حالًا‬
Is everything all right?
‫كل شيء على ما يرام، صحيح؟‬
Yeah... It's all going well.
‫أجل، لا توجد مشاكل‬
That's good. This is a very special day for us.
‫جيد، هذا اليوم مميز أكثر من أي يوم آخر‬
Don't drop your guard. Lick.
‫لا ترخي دفاعك-بيرورين‬
I know.
‫مفهوم‬
It's 12 o'clock! It's 12 o'clock!
‫إنها الساعة 12، إنها الساعة 12‬
Ladies and gentlemen! It's time for today's main event!
‫إنه الحدث الرئيسي لهذا اليوم أيتها السيدات والسادة‬
The 35th daughter of the Charlotte family, Madam Charlotte Pudding,
‫الابنة 35 لعائلة شارلوت، شارلوت بودينغ-ساما‬
and the third son of Vinsmoke family, Prince Vinsmoke Sanji...
‫والابن الثالث لعائلة فينسموك، فينسموك سانجي-ساما‬
Their royal wedding...
‫الزفاف الملكي‬
starts now!
‫يبدأ الآن‬
♪ Marriage! ♪
‫♪ زواج ♪‬
♪ Marriage! Marriage! ♪
‫♪ زواج، زواج ♪‬
That's awesome!
‫رائع‬
Without further ado, here are the bride and groom!
‫ها هما العريس والعروس دون مقدمات إضافية‬
Emperor Big Mom and her pirates
‫طاقم قراصنة الإمبراطورة بيغ مام‬
and the evil army Germa 66:
‫والجيش الشيطاني جيرما 66‬
This young couple will unite their notorious families!
‫هؤلاء اليافعان سيحققان أحلامهم‬ ‫بمشاركة سُبل عوائلهما شائعة الصيت‬
Mariage de raison !
‫بالزواج السياسي‬
When these two tie the knot, it will be the start of a fearsome new era!
‫بارتباطهما، ستزدهر زهرة شر جديدة في هذا العالم‬
Give it up for them!
‫رحبوا بهما‬
Look at that!
‫انظر هناك‬
For this extremely beautiful day!
‫من أجل هذا اليوم الجميل‬
Give it up!
‫رحبوا بهما‬
Unbelievable!
‫ذلك الوغد‬
What a great actor!
‫يا له من ممثل بارع‬
The bloody wedding has begun!
‫موعد الزفاف الدموي قد بدء الآن‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
The ceremony has begun! Luffy!
‫لقد بدأ الحفل يا لوفي‬
I'm still hungry...
‫يمكنني تناول المزيد‬
Wake up!
‫استيقظ‬
Do you wanna let Sanji down?!
‫هل ستتخلى عن سانجي؟‬
Hey! Is there any way to wake him up?!
‫أنتم، أما من طريقة لإيقاظه؟‬
He was running around the forest right before he fell asleep so...
‫لقد أرهق نفسه بالركض‬ ‫في أرجاء الغابة قبل خلوده للنوم، لذا...‬
Food is the only thing that'll wake him up.
‫لن يستيقظ من سُباته العميق سوى بالطعام‬
Hey, do you have any meat?! We don't have time!
‫أنتم، ألديكم بعض اللحم؟ الوقت يداهمنا‬
– Meat? – He's gonna have breakfast now?
‫لحم؟‬
This is your requiem!
‫هذه موسيقى جنازتك‬
Just listen to it with that stupid look on your face, Sanji!
‫استمع إليها بهذه الملامح الغبية التي تعلو محياك يا سانجي‬
Thank you, Sanji-san !
‫سانجي-سان، شكرًا لك‬
Sanji-san, I'm...
‫سانجي-سان، أنا...‬
so happy!
‫سعيدة للغاية‬
P... P-P-P-P-Pudding-chan...
‫بـ-بـ-بـ-بـ-بودينغ-تشان‬
Me... Me too!
‫وأنا... وأنا أيضًا‬
No! No! Stay rational!
‫كلا، كلا، حافظ على رباطة جأشك‬
If you're not careful, you'll...
‫إن فقدت تركيزك، سوف...‬
you'll get killed!
‫سوف تُقتل‬
♪ Marriage! ♪
‫♪ زواج ♪‬
♪ Tough love... ♪
‫♪ حبٌّ صعب ♪‬
♪ I've been there... ♪
‫♪ وكنا نعيش ♪‬
♪ Bitter love... ♪
‫♪ حبٌّ مرير ♪‬
♪ Yet despite it all, when it's true love... ♪
‫♪ وقعت في الحب، وقعت بعمق، وتأذيت ♪‬
♪ I must reach the aisle ♪
‫♪ ووصلت لنهاية الطريق ♪‬
♪ Even if I were drenched with rain ♪
‫♪ حتى لو هطل المطر عليّ ♪‬
♪ Even if spears rain down on me ♪
‫♪ حتى لو هطل المطر عليّ بغزارة ♪‬
♪ Never let that hand go! ♪
‫♪ لن أفلت يدك ♪‬
– Head Chef!
‫رئيس الطهاة -‬
Head Chef!
‫رئيس الطهاة‬
♪ It's time to unveil the... ♪
‫♪ حان الوقت للكشف عن ♪‬
♪ wedding cake! ♪
‫♪ كعكة الزفاف ♪‬
Bravo!
‫أحسنتم‬
Beautiful! Brilliant!
‫جميلة ورائعة‬
It's so big and fancy!
‫يا لضخامتها وفخامتها‬
Looks delicious!
‫تبدو شهية‬
What a magnificent wedding cake!
‫إنها كعكة زفاف مدهشة‬
You did a wonderful job, Streusen! I have to give you praise!
‫عمل مبهر يا سترويزن، تستحق عليه كل الثناء والتقدير‬
It's more than I deserve!
‫لا أستحق هذا الإطراء‬
I can't wait to eat it!
‫لنأكلها بسرعة‬
How lovely! Our altar is on top of the sweet cake!
‫جميل، لا أصدق أننا سنعقد قراننا بوجود هذه الكعكة الجميلة‬
You are what's lovely!
‫كلا، أنتِ أجمل منها‬
Oh, stop! Come on, Sanji-san !
‫كلا، كفّ عن إحراجي يا سانجي-سان‬
Just drop dead already!
‫مُت بسرعة‬
Pudding-chan looks so beautiful... It feels like I'm watching my younger self.
‫بودينغ-تشان جميلة للغاية، إنها تذكرني بأيام شبابي‬
How many decades ago?
‫قبل كم من العقود كان ذلك؟‬
You must have a death wish.
‫أظن أنّ أحدهم يريد الموت‬
Ouch!
‫مؤلم‬
Enjoy it while you can, my guests.
‫استمتعوا بوقتكم يا ضيوفي الأعزاء‬
The climax is approaching...
‫العرض الرئيسي سيحين قريبًا‬
It'll all be over before you know it...
‫سينتهي الأمر بلمح البصر‬
Please. Enjoy the ceremony from these VIP seats.
‫تفضلوا بمشاهدة مراسم الزفاف من مقاعد الشخصيات المهمة‬
It's about to start!
‫والآن ستبدأ...‬
The bloodbath!
‫المجزرة‬
At the moment of the wedding kiss...
‫عندما تحين قبلة الزفاف...‬
...the bloody banquet will begin.
‫ستبدأ الحفلة الدموية‬
I'm sorry! But you Vinsmokes are in my way!
‫المعذرة، ولكن يجب أن تهلكوا يا فينسموك‬
Sanji's lucky!
‫يا له من محظوظ ذلك السانجي‬
If I'd known she was that pretty, I wouldn't have minded marrying her.
‫لو علمت بأنها بهذا الجمال، لما مانعت الزواج منها‬
Marrying Big Mom's daughter? Idiot.
‫تتزوج ابنة بيغ مام؟ هل أنت أحمق؟‬
He's a sacrifice. Don't forget.
‫لا تنسى بأنه كبش فداء‬
Once he's married, he'll be under Big Mom's control forever.
‫بمجرد زواجه بها، سيمضي بقية حياته تحت سيطرة بيغ مام‬
You're right. It wouldn't be worth it.
‫أصبت، هذا آخر شيء أريده‬
I see... We're surrounded by the Charlotte siblings.
‫فهمت، إننا محاطون بأبناء شارلوت‬
We have nowhere to run.
‫مما جعلنا أهدافًا سهلة المنال‬
And we're unarmed, so we're basically sitting ducks.
‫سينتهي أمرنا بمجرد أن ينقض علينا هؤلاء الوحوش‬
That's how it should be...
‫هذا جيد‬
Germa is a kingdom that shouldn't exist.
‫فمملكة جريما لا تستحق الوجود‬
But...
‫لكن...‬
Sanji...
‫سانجي...‬
I want you to get away.
‫أنت وحدك أريدك أن تهرب‬
You have a plan, right? Can I trust you?
‫أيمكنني الوثوق بأنّ لديك خطة ما...‬
Luffy-kun !
‫يا لوفي-كن؟‬
In sickness and in health,
‫في السرّاء والضرّاء‬
for richer, for poorer,
‫وفي الثراء والفقر‬
to have and to hold,
‫سأظل بجانبك‬
till death do you part...
‫حتى يفرّقنا الموت‬
Hurry up, guys! We don't have time!
‫اسرعوا يا رفاق، الوقت يداهمنا‬
Do you pledge yourself to love and to be loyal to each other?
‫هل تتعهدان بالحب والوفاء لبعضكما؟‬
My wish is finally coming true!
‫أمنيتي ستتحقق أخيرًا‬
What's wrong, Pudding? Why are you going to collapse?!
‫ما الخطب يا بودينغ؟ لِمَ ستنهارين؟‬
Then, you may lift the veil and kiss the bride.
‫والآن يمكنك رفع حجابها وتقبيلها‬
Is something wrong, Brother?
‫أهناك خطبٌ ما يا أخي؟‬
You saw the future, Katakuri!
‫لقد رأيت المستقبل يا كاتاكوري‬
I'll lift your veil.
‫سأرفع حجابك‬
Okay.
‫أجل‬
Sanji, take a good look...
‫انظر جيدًا يا سانجي‬
at...
‫إلى...‬
at my creepy...
‫إلى ما سيخيفك‬
third eye!
‫عيني الثالثة‬
Good boy.
‫فتىً جيد‬
Stay like that...
‫ابق هكذا‬
What a beautiful eye!
‫يا لها من عين جميلة‬
I'm sorry! When I saw it up close, I couldn't help it...
‫المعذرة، عندما رأيتها عن قرب، أُغرمت بها‬
What is she doing?!
‫ما الذي تفعله؟‬
Don't hesitate, Pudding!
‫إياكِ أن تترددي يا بودينغ‬
Pudding... -chan ?
‫بودينغ-تشان؟‬
What is he saying?
‫ما الذي يقوله؟‬
Everyone will be watching the groom, Sanji...
‫عندما يدخل العريس سانجي للقاعة‬
He'll see your third eye for the first time!
‫سيرى عينك الثالثة لأول مرة‬
In that moment, he'll see his beautiful bride's creepy face,
‫في اللحظة التي يرى فيها الوجه الحقيقي والمخيف لعروسته الجميلة‬
and he'll be distracted for a moment!
‫سيتراجع للوراء قليلًا‬
Screw him!
‫لا تعبث معي‬
What is he thinking?!
‫بمَ يفكر؟‬
Ever since I was born, I've never been told...!
‫منذ أن ولدت، لم يخبرني أحد...‬
Not a single person has ever told me that this eye is beautiful!
‫لم يقل لي أي شخص بأنّ هذه العين جميلة‬
What's wrong, Pudding?! Just shoot him!
‫ما الخطب يا بودينغ؟ اقتليه بسرعة‬
No one's ever...
‫لا أحد إطلاقًا...‬
Even if you're my daughter, I can't deny that's creepy...
‫على الرغم من أنني والدتك إلا أنني أرى هذه العين غريبة‬
Grow out your bangs, Pudding.
‫حاولي إطالة غرّتك يا بودينغ‬
Yes... I understand, ma'am...
‫حاضر، فهمت‬
She's a monster!
‫إنها وحش‬
So creepy!
‫مخيفة للغاية‬
What's wrong with this kid?!
‫ما خطب هذه الفتاة؟‬
Look! She's a freak!
‫انظروا إلى عين الوحش‬
Don't do it!
‫توقف‬
How's that, freak?!
‫ما رأيك أيها الوحش؟‬
Freak! Freak!
‫وحش، وحش‬
I'm not gonna let you make fun of me!
‫لن أقف مكتوفة اليدين بينما تسخرون منّي‬
You stupid trash...
‫كل واحدٍ منكم...‬
I'll wipe you all out!
‫سأقتلكم جميعًا‬
Run!
‫اهربوا‬
Pudding-chan...
‫بودينغ-تشان‬
Screw you!
‫لا تعبث معي‬
I'm gonna kill you!
‫أنا سأقوم بقتلك‬
I'm an ugly freak!
‫أنا مجرد وحش بشع‬
Hey, did you forget the plan, Pudding?!
‫مهلًا، ماذا حلّ بالخطة يا بودينغ؟‬
Pudding-chan, are you okay?
‫بودينغ-تشان، هل أنتِ بخير؟‬
You do it, priest!
‫افعلها أنت أيها القِس‬
That's no good! He'll miss!
‫لا فائدة، سيتفاداها‬
He dodged!
‫تفاداها‬
Straw Hat! Now's the time!
‫قبعة القش، حان دورك‬
That's the gunshot, Luffy!
‫تلك إشارة إطلاق النار يا لوفي‬
Great! We'll make it!
‫عظيم، سأصل في الوقت المناسب‬
What was that gunshot?!
‫ماذا كانت تلك الطلقة؟‬
The priest fired!
‫أطلق القِس النار‬
No, he got shot!
‫كلا، بل هو من أُصيب‬
Why?!
‫لماذا؟‬
What's going on?!
‫ما الذي يحدث؟‬
Is this...?!
‫أهذا...‬
What the hell is going on?! Katakuri, what happened to Pudding?!
‫ما الذي يجري؟‬
We have a bigger problem! It's an unanticipated situation, Mama!
‫لدينا مشكلة أكبر، ثمة أمر غير متوقع على وشك الحدوث يا ماما‬
Not even I can do anything!
‫حتى أنا لا يسعني فعل شيء‬
What should we do?! Sanji hasn't been shot!
‫ما العمل؟ لم يُصب سانجي بأي أذى‬
Is the plan still on?
‫أما زالت الخطة مستمرة؟‬
Let's go!
‫هيا بنا‬
I'm sorry, Mama! I had no choice but to do what they told me to!
‫أنا أعتذر يا ماما، لا أملك خيارًا سوى تنفيذ أوامرهم‬
We'll take Sanji back!
‫سنستعيد سانجي‬
What the...?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
I can't stop them!
‫لا يمكنني إيقاف ما سيحدث‬
They'll come out of there!
‫سيخرجون من هناك‬
Big Mom!
‫بيغ مام‬